Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Officers and Staff-Administrative Files, 1962-2004
  - Subseries IV:G: Brenda Stokely, 1982-2004.
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1990-1997; cuid7239 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1996-2003; cuid7240 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1997-2003; cuid7241 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 1998-2002; cuid7242 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2001-2003; cuid7243 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2001-2003; cuid7244 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2001-2004; cuid7245 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2003; cuid7246 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--General Administrative, 2003-2004; cuid7247 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Grievances, 1996-2003; cuid7248 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Grievances, 2000-2002; cuid7249 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Grievance, Brenda Stokely, 1994-1995; cuid7250 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Health Benefits, 1999, undated; cuid7251 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Negotiations (I), 1999; cuid7252 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Negotiations (II), 1999; cuid7253 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Agencies: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA)--Sexual Harassment, 1996-2004; cuid7254 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1997-2000; cuid7255 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Benefit Information, 1982-1997; cuid7256 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Black Workers for Justice, 1991-1996; cuid7257 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Case Assignments, 1997-1998; cuid7258 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, Articles, 1992-1999; cuid7259 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): Youth Committee/General, 1995-1999; cuid7260 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Community Resources, Undated; cuid7261 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence/Memoranda, 1997-2004; cuid7262 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - CSAE Federal Credit Union, 1992; cuid7263 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 1995-1997; cuid7264 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 1997-1998; cuid7265 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 1997-2004; cuid7266 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 2002-2003; cuid7267 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - DC 1707 General Administrative, 2003; cuid7268 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Educational Alliance, 1998; cuid7269 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Ephemera, 1997-1999, undated; cuid7270 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Family and Medical Leave Act (FMLA), 1994-1996; cuid7271 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Flyers/Circulars/Leaflets, 1997-2004, undated; cuid7272 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Funding/Grant Information, Undated; cuid7273 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Hardship, 1998, undated; cuid7274 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Health and Safety Training, 1998, undated; cuid7275 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Labor/Black History, Undated; cuid7276 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Labor/General, 2000, undated; cuid7277 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Labor Party/New York Labor History, 1997-2003; cuid7278 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Labor Party/New York Labor Party, 2000. undated; cuid7279 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Labor Resources, 1997, undated; cuid7280 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Local 215 Education Committee, 1998-1999; cuid7281 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Local 215 General Administrative, 1996-1997; cuid7282 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Local 215 General Administrative, 1997-1999; cuid7283 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Local 215 General Administrative (bulk Little Flower), 1997-1999; cuid7284 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Negotiation Notes, 1996-1997; cuid7285 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Neuro-Linguistic Programming (NLP), Undated; cuid7286 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1997-1999; cuid7287 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, 1996-1997; cuid7288 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - New York State AFL-CIO, 1997-1998; cuid7289 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Notes/Meeting Notes, 1997; cuid7290 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Notes/Meeting Notes, 1999-2000, undated; cuid7291 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Organizing, 1999; cuid7292 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Politics/Protests, 1995-2003; cuid7293 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Professional, CSW, 1991-1997; cuid7294 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Queens College Worker Education Extension Center Graduation, 1990-1997; cuid7295 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Shop Steward Notes, Undated; cuid7296 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Strike Flyers/Information, 1994, undated; cuid7297 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Workplace Violence Prevention, 1996; cuid7298 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Floppy disk: New York Association for New Americans (NYANA), Undated; cuid7299 (Box 47)
  - Subseries IV:H: G.L. Tyler, 1991-2001.
    Tyler's titles at DC 1707 include Director of Organizing and Political Action, and Political Action Director (circa 2004). His files mostly relate to organizing and to specific agencies.
    - Allen Health Care Services, 1999-2000; cuid7300 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha Day Care Center, 1998; cuid7301 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Bryan Home Care, 1998; cuid7302 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Center for Employment Opportunities, 1998; cuid7303 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Central Brooklyn Coordinating Council, 1998; cuid7304 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - DC 1707 Political Action Liaison Program, Undated; cuid7305 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Ferncliff Manor for the Retarded, Inc., 1997-1998; cuid7306 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Grievances, 1998-1999; cuid7307 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Home Assistance Personnel, Inc., 1997-1998; cuid7308 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Labor-Religion Coalition, 1998; cuid7309 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Little Flower Children's Services, 1997-1998; cuid7310 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Living Resources, 1997-1999, undated; cuid7311 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Local 205, 1997; cuid7312 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Masterson's Day Care Center, 1997; cuid7313 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Metro New York Health Care, 1999; cuid7314 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1995-2001; cuid7315 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Organizing (I), 1997-1999; cuid7316 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Organizing (II), 1997-1999; cuid7317 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Organizing Campaign Manuals, 1998, undated; cuid7318 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Pine Street Day Care Center, 1999; cuid7319 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Rena's Residence for Adults, 1997; cuid7320 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Res-Care, Inc., 1998; cuid7321 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Right to Join a Union, Undated; cuid7322 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Saint Christopher's-Jennie Clarkson Child Care Services, Inc., 1998; cuid7323 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Special Citizens Futures Unlimited, 1997-2000; cuid7324 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Staff Performance Evaluation Forms, Undated; cuid7325 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Strategic Planning, 2000; cuid7326 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Tiny Towne Child Care Center, Inc., 1991-1993; cuid7327 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Union Contract Handout, Undated; cuid7328 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Urban Family Health, 1997-1998; cuid7329 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - US HomeCare, 1998, undated; cuid7330 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Venture Day Treatment Center/Camp Venture, 1997-1999; cuid7331 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Series V: Publications and Publicity Files, 1982-2004
  Files contain research notes for and drafts of articles, presumably for publication in DC 1707 Voice or Council newsletters. Subjects include DC 1707's agencies, politics, issues of interest to Council members, and profiles of members. Also included are drafts of columns written by DC 1707 and AFSCME officers. Also included in this series are 199 floppy disks, which appear to contain articles, drafts, photos and graphics for DC 1707 publications.
  - Albany: La Salle Academy, Hope House, 2002, undated; cuid7332 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Allen Home Health Care, 2000-2003, undated; cuid7333 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 2004; cuid7334 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME: Women the Force of the Future Conference, Undated; cuid7335 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - AFSCME New York State: Lobby Day, 2002-2003; cuid7336 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - AMIT, Undated; cuid7337 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Freeman Home, 2002, undated; cuid7338 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Articles, [1982-1983]; cuid7339 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Articles, [1984], undated; cuid7340 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Articles and Columns, 2002-2004, undated; cuid7341 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Articles and Columns: DC 1707 and AFSCME Officers, 2002, undated; cuid7342 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Beck Notice, 2001; cuid7343 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization, Local 107, 2003, undated; cuid7344 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Cargill, Undated; cuid7345 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Caring Community, Inc., 2003; cuid7346 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Cartoons, 2004; cuid7347 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Cintas, 2004, undated; cuid7348 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Coca-Cola Colombia, 2003, undated; cuid7349 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Condolences, 2004, undated; cuid7350 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Correctional Services Corp, 2003; cuid7351 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Day Care, 2004, undated; cuid7352 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Day Care Voice Newsletter, 2004, undated; cuid7353 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - DC 1707, 2003-2004, undated; cuid7354 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - DC 1707 Summit, 2004; cuid7355 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit, Undated; cuid7356 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Education Department Program/Education, 2003, undated; cuid7357 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Election, 2004: Compassion Action, cuid7358 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Election, 2004: Editorial, cuid7359 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Election, 2004: New Hampshire, cuid7360 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Events and Services, 2003, undated; cuid7361 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Services (FEGS), 2003, undated; cuid7362 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Fields, C. Virginia--Manhattan Borough President, Undated; cuid7363 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Financial Documents, 2004, undated; cuid7364 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Flyers, [1986], [2003-2004]; cuid7365 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Front Page, 2002, undated; cuid7366 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - George Jr., Raglan: Letter to New York Times, 2004; cuid7367 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Grievance Training, 2004; cuid7368 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Grievances/Arbitration Awards, 2002-2004, undated; cuid7369 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Hands Across America, 1986; cuid7370 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Head Start, 2002-2003, undated; cuid7371 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Home Attendants Personnel Inc., 2002-2004; cuid7372 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Home Care, 2004, undated; cuid7373 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Home Care Employees/Homemakers, 2003-2004; cuid7374 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Homecoming, 2004; cuid7375 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Hyatt Hotels, Undated; cuid7376 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Immigrant Rights, 2003, undated; cuid7377 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Institute of International Education, Undated; cuid7378 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - International Rescue Committee, 2002, undated; cuid7379 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Iraq War Protests, Undated; cuid7380 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children's Services (JBFCS), Undated; cuid7381 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Community Centers Metrowest, 2003, undated; cuid7382 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Labor Day, 2003-[2004]; cuid7383 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Latino Affairs Committee, [2003]; cuid7384 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Leake and Watts, 2003, undated; cuid7385 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Lexington Children's Center, 2004, undated; cuid7386 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Living Wage Hearing, 2002, undated; cuid7387 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Local 205, 2002, undated; cuid7388 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Local 205 Bake Sale, 2003; cuid7389 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Local 215, 2002; cuid7390 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Local 389 Financial Reports, 2002, undated; cuid7391 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Long Island Head Start, Undated; cuid7392 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Louise Wise Services, 2004, undated; cuid7393 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Low Memorial Child Care Center, 2003, undated; cuid7394 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Madison Square Garden Protest, 2004, undated; cuid7395 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - McEnroe Memorial Meeting, 2002; cuid7396 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - McMillan/Tart Indictment, 2003, undated; cuid7397 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Metrocare Home Services, 2002-2003; cuid7398 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Mid-Westchester Jewish Community Center, Scarsdale, Undated; cuid7399 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Million Worker March, [2004]; cuid7400 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense Fund, 2004, undated; cuid7401 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - New York Society for the Deaf, 2003-2004, undated; cuid7402 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - 92nd St. YM and YWHA, 2004; cuid7403 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Organizing, Undated; cuid7404 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Organizing Training, 2004; cuid7405 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Paul J. Cooper Center for Human Services, 2004, undated; cuid7406 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Pleasantville Cottage School, Undated; cuid7407 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Political Action, 2004, undated; cuid7408 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Political Endorsements, 2002-2004; cuid7409 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Powell, Odessa (Local 389): Awards, [2003]; cuid7410 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Press Conference, 2002, undated; cuid7411 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Production, 2003, undated; cuid7412 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - Profiles, Undated; cuid7413 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - Rainbow Early Head Start Center, 2002, undated; cuid7414 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - Richmond Early Learning Day Care Center, 2004, undated; cuid7415 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - Robinson, Annette--Assemblywoman, Undated; cuid7416 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - Shield Institute, 2002, undated; cuid7417 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - Sources--July, 1982, undated; cuid7418 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - Sources--September, 1982; cuid7419 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - Sources--October, 1982, undated; cuid7420 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - South Bronx Head Start, Undated; cuid7421 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - St. Agatha's Home/St. Christopher's/St. Mark's Day Care Center, 2002-2003, undated; cuid7422 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - Susan E. Wagner Day Care Center, 2003, undated; cuid7423 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - "Talking It Up", 2002, undated; cuid7424 (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - "This Is Our Union", 1982; cuid7425 (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - United Jewish Federation--New Jersey, 2003, undated; cuid7426 (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - Weekly Schedules, 2002; cuid7427 (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - Weingarten Rules, Undated; cuid7428 (Box 43, Folder 67)
  - Williams Memorial Residence, Salvation Army, 2003, undated; cuid7429 (Box 43, Folder 68)
  - Floppy Disks, 1998-2003, undated; cuid7430 (Box 47)
- Series VI: General Files, 1980-2001
  This series includes material relating to organizations and subjects of interest to the Council, organized alphabetically. A substantial number of files document DC 1707's involvement in the Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) and the Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW).
  - AFSCME, 1991-1999, undated; cuid7431 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - AFSCME: Handbooks, 1980-1994; cuid7432 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - AFSCME: Judicial Panel International Executive Board Report, Aug 1998; cuid7433 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME: Judicial Panel International Executive Board Report, Mar 1999; cuid7434 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - AFSCME: Membership Education and Mobilization for Organizing--Training Manual, Undated; cuid7435 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Black and Puerto Rican Caucus, 1997; cuid7436 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1990-1998; cuid7437 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): Constitution, 1987-1990; cuid7438 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): Conventions, 1997-2000; cuid7439 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): Flyers, 1995-1996, undated; cuid7440 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): General Administrative, 1997, undated; cuid7441 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): James "Jim" Bell Scholarship Award--Applicants A-D, 1996-1999; cuid7442 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): James "Jim" Bell Scholarship Award--Applicants E-Z, 1995-1999; cuid7443 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): James "Jim" Bell Scholarship Award--Applications and Review Forms, [1996-1999]; cuid7444 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): James "Jim" Bell Scholarship Award--Program, 1999; cuid7445 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): New York Chapter, 1994-1999; cuid7446 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): New York Chapter, 1997-2000; cuid7447 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): Region 1 Conference, 1997; cuid7448 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU): Youth Committee, 2000; cuid7449 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Bargaining Guide, 2000; cuid7450 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Correspondence, 1996-1999; cuid7451 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Correspondence from Gloria Johnson/National Office, 1997; cuid7452 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Correspondence from Gloria Johnson/National Office, 1998-1999; cuid7453 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Financial Records, 1995-2001; cuid7454 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): General Administrative, 1998-1999, undated; cuid7455 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Executive Board Meeting, Feb 1997; cuid7456 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Officers Council Meeting, Aug 1997; cuid7457 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--Biennial Convention, Nov 1997; cuid7458 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events, 1998; cuid7459 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events, Jan 1998; cuid7460 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Executive Board Meeting, Mar 1998; cuid7461 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Executive Board Meeting, Jun 1998; cuid7462 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Officers Council Meeting, Jun 1998; cuid7463 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--Violence Against Women, Jun 1998; cuid7464 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Executive Board Meeting, Sep 1998; cuid7465 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Officers Council Meeting, Nov 1998; cuid7466 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Officers Council Meeting, Apr 1999; cuid7467 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Executive Board Meeting, Jun 1999; cuid7468 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--Biennial Convention, Sep 1999; cuid7469 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Officers Council Meeting, Oct 1999; cuid7470 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--Unions Against Domestic Violence, Nov 1999; cuid7471 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Executive Board Meeting (I), Mar 2000; cuid7472 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--National Executive Board Meeting (II), Mar 2000; cuid7473 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): Meetings and Events--Biennial Convention, 2001; cuid7474 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW): New York City Chapter/Elections Committee, 1980-1990; cuid7475 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Collective Bargaining, Undated; cuid7476 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Day Care/Child Care: General, 1992-1994; cuid7477 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Day Care: New York City Health Code, Undated; cuid7478 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Education, 1991-1994; cuid7479 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Ephemera, 1996-1999, undated; cuid7480 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Foster Care, 1998, undated; cuid7481 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Head Start Program: Performance Standards, 1998; cuid7482 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Health and Safety, 1991-1993, undated; cuid7483 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Legislative (Federal), 1992-1994; cuid7484 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Legislative (New York State), 1991-1998; cuid7485 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - National Committee on Pay Equity, 1999; cuid7486 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - New York City Budget: City Project, 1993-1995; cuid7487 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - New York City Temporary Task Force on Child Care Funding, 1995; cuid7488 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Organizing, 1997; cuid7489 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - People's Weekly World Luncheon, 1997; cuid7490 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Political Contributions, 2001; cuid7491 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Social Security, 1998, undated; cuid7492 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Staff Training, 1981-1987, undated; cuid7493 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Stewards Training, 1988, undated; cuid7494 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Voter Education Kit, Undated; cuid7495 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Welfare and Social Services, 1991-1993; cuid7496 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Reform, 1996-1997; cuid7497 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Wilson, Susan: Articles, 1989-1991; cuid7498 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Working Committee on HIV, Children, and Families, 1996; cuid7499 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - 13 reels of 16 mm microfilm, 1950-1991; cuid7500 (Box 47)
    13 reels of 16 mm microfilm containing DC 170 contracts from 1950-1990, clippings, arbitration awards, grievances, day care pension plans, YWCA national board records, victims information bureau records, JCC delegate assembly records 1974-1991, executive board and joint city council minutes 1963 and 1966, JNF arbitrations, and child development center records.
  - Floppy disk: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU)--New York Chapter, Undated; cuid7501 (Box 47)
- Series VII: Photographs, 1980-2004
  - Black and White Photographs; Photographs for Publicity, undated; cuid7502 (Box 52)
  - Color Photographs, undated; cuid7503 (Box 53)
  - Contact Sheets and Negatives I, undated; cuid7504 (Box 54)
  - Contact Sheets and Negatives II, undated; cuid7505 (Box 55)
  - Slides, VHS, Audiocassettes and CDs, undated; cuid7506 (Box 56)